Vivienne Malone-Mayes papers, Inclusive: 1966-1977, undated; Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Vivienne Malone-Mayes papers
Inclusive: 1966-1977, undated; Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
2072
Mayes, Vivienne Malone, 1932 - 1995
This collection contains twenty-five document boxes.
The Vivienne Malone-Mayes papers consists of correspondence, minutes, reports and other records related to the donor's terms as a member and Chairperson of the Board of Trustees for the Heart of Texas Region Mental Health Mental Retardation Center in Waco, Texas. The collection also contains personal materials and coursework Dr. Malone-Mayes assigned in her mathematics courses at Baylor University.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Excellent.
Biography/Profile
Vivienne Lucille Malone, the daughter of Pizarro and Vera Estelle Allen Malone, was born in Waco, Texas, on 1932 February 10. As a member of the African-American community in the South, Malone faced significant challenges growing up, particularly in the area of education. However, thanks in large part to the encouragement of her parents, who were both educators, Vivienne thrived in the pursuit of knowledge despite the obstacles that existed.
From her earliest days as a student at North Seventh Street Elementary School in Waco, Vivienne experienced the challenges associated with racially segregated school systems. She did not, however, allow her circumstances to deter her. In 1948, she graduated from A.J. Moore High School at the age of sixteen. Malone then attended Fisk University where she earned her bachelor’s degree (1952) and master’s degree (1954). While at Fisk, Mayes changed her degree from medicine to mathematics after coming under the tutelage of Evelyn Granville, one of the first of two African-American women to earn her Ph.D. in mathematics. It was also during this time that Vivienne married her husband, James Mayes.
After a teaching stint at Paul Quinn College, Malone-Mayes decided to pursue doctoral work in the field of mathematics. In 1961, she applied to Baylor’s graduate program but was denied entry because the school had not yet been fully integrated. She was finally accepted into the University of Texas where she became only the fifth African-American woman in the nation to earn a Ph.D. in mathematics (1966).
In 1966, Dr. Malone-Mayes returned to Baylor University where she was hired to a full-time position as a professor in the mathematics department. She was the first African-American hired to such a position in Baylor history. She went on to have a successful, lengthy career in her field, serving on several boards and committees of note. She retired in 1994 due to ill health.
Alongside her academic pursuits, Dr. Malone-Mayes remained active in the local community. Since the days of her childhood, Vivienne was an active member of New Hope Baptist Church. She also served on various boards for Family Counseling and Children Services, Goodwill Industries, and the Heart of Texas Region Mental Health and Mental Retardation Center.
Dr. Malone-Mayes passed away in 1995 June 9 at the age of sixty-three.
Scope and Content
The Vivienne Malone-Mayes papers include 1966 to 1977, the years immediately following Dr. Malone-Mayes' attainment of her Ph.D. in mathematics from the University of Texas. There are a few personal materials and mathematics coursework located in the collection. However, the overwhelming majority of this record group consists of correspondence, reports, and minutes from the Heart of Texas Region Mental Health and Mental Retardation Center in Waco. Dr. Malone-Mayes was active in the direction of this organization, serving as a board member and Chairman of the Board during the 1970s.
Arrangement
The Vivienne Malone-Mayes papers were previously organized into eight document boxes. No finding aid existed for the collection.
An intern started processing the collection in 2013 April by creating a preliminary processing plan and an accession record worksheet. She organized the collection into three series: I. Mental Health Mental Retardation Center, II. Baylor Mathematics Department, and III. Personal Materials. The proposed organization has been applied to the collection.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 2072. Acquired 1979-11-29
Related Resources
Items in related collections
[Waco] New Hope Baptist Church records, Inclusive: 1875-1988, Bulk: 1922-1985
Related references
Blount, Luke. “Trail Blazer: The Story of Baylor’s First African-American Professor.” Baylor Line: Magazine of the Baylor Alumni Association. Accessed 2013 April 3.
Carr, Daphne L. “Vivienne Malone-Mayes: The Early Years, 1932-1966.” M.A. thesis, Baylor University, 1998.
Jones, Dennis R. and Sheila Allee. “Texas Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation.” Handbook of Texas Online. Accessed 2013 June 3.
Malone-Mayes, Vivienne L. “Oral Memoirs of Vivienne Lucille Malone-Mayes.” Interview by Rebecca Sharpless. Analog tape, 1987 July 29, transcript, Baylor University Institute for Oral History, Baylor University. Accessed 2020 May 1.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Malone-Mayes, Vivienne.
Subjects
African Americans -- Education (Higher).; Baylor University -- Faculty.; Mathematics -- Study and teaching.; Mental health -- Texas.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Minutes (Records); Periodicals.; Reports.
- Mental Health Mental Retardation Center, 1967-1977, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Excellent.
  Biography/Profile
  This series, the largest in the collection, contains minutes, correspondence, reports, and other materials produced by the Mental Health Mental Retardation Center in Waco, Texas. Dr. Vivienne Malone-Mayes served as a member and chair of the board of trustees during the early 1970s.
  Arrangement
  Due to the substantial size of this series, the materials have been divided into subseries. There are seven subseries organized chronologically according to the year in which the materials were created: I. 1967-1972, II. 1973, III. 1974, IV. 1975, V. 1976, VI. 1977, VII. Undated.
  - 1967-1972, 1
    This subseries contains materials produced by the Mental Health Mental Retardation Center in Waco from 1967 to 1972. Materials include minutes and reports.
    The materials within this subseries are organized alphabetically by type.
    - Minutes: Action Planning Council, 1967 April-June (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Action Planning Council, 1967 July-September (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Action Planning Council, 1967 November-December (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1972 November-December (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Report: Monthly, 1972 November (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Report: Program Evaluation, 1972 December 6-8 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Transcript: Program Evaluation: Feedback, 1972 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1973, 2
    This subseries contains materials produced by the Mental Health Mental Retardation Center in Waco in 1973. Materials include reports, correspondence, and minutes.
    The materials within this subseries is organized alphabetically according to type of material.
    - Application: Developmental Disabilities Services Grant (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Application: Developmental Disabilities Services Grant (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Book: Standards for Community Agencies, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brochure: “Developing Human Potentials”, circa 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: General, 1973 October-December (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1973 January (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1973 October-December (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Children’s Guidance Center, 1973 December (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Real Estate, 1973 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1973 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1973 October 11-December 6 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Program Directors, 1973 September 11-24 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlet: “Rules, Regulations, and Standards”, 1973 September (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Periodicals: Impact, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Printed Materials: General, circa 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Proposal: Alcohol and Drug Abuse Program (1 of 5), 1973 January 9-10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Proposal: Alcohol and Drug Abuse Program (2 of 5), 1973 January 9-10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Proposal: Alcohol and Drug Abuse Program (3 of 5), 1973 January 9-10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Proposal: Alcohol and Drug Abuse Program (4 of 5), 1973 January 9-10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Proposal: Alcohol and Drug Abuse Program (5 of 5), 1973 January 9-10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Proposal: Tacoma-Pierce County Comprehensive Mental Health Center, 1973 June (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Report: Equal Employment Opportunity Program, 1973 December 29 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Report: Examination, 1973 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Report: Expenditure, 1973 January 11 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Report: Expenditure, 1973 October 9 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Report: Expenditure, 1973 December 28 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Report: Staff Evaluation Form, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Report: Standards: Accreditation Council for Facilities for the Mentally Retarded, 1973 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Report: United Fund of Waco, 1973 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1973 February-September (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1973 December (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1974, 3
    This subseries contains materials produced by the Heart of Texas Mental Health Mental Retardation Center in 1974. These include correspondence, reports, and minutes.
    The materials within this subseries are organized alphabetically according to type of material.
    - Address: Bill Hobby: Texas United Community Services, 1974 March 19 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Address: Ron Luke: “The Issues of Mental Health Services in Texas”, 1974 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Application: Federal Grant, 1974 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Application: Social Services Intake Summary, circa 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Article: Dimensions: “The Happiest Place in Town-They Can If We Will”, 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Balance Sheet: General, 1974 August-November (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: General, 1974 February (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: General, 1974 May-June (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: General, 1974 October-November (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 January-February (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 April-May (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 June (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 July (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 August-September (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 November (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1974 December (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Executive Director, 1974 February-March (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Executive Director, 1974 April-May (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Vivienne Malone-Mayes, 1974 April-July (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Diagram: Organizational Chart, 1974 December (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1974 January-June (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1974 October-November (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Financial Documents: Proposed Halfway House, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Advisory Committee, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 January-February (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 April 25 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 May (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 August 15 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 November (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Packet: Board of Trustee Orientation, 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Packet: Employment Policies (1 of 3), circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Packet: Employment Policies (2 of 3), circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Packet: Employment Policies (3 of 3), circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Periodical: Impact, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Printed Materials: General, 1974 February-April (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Printed Materials: General, 1974 May-July (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Printed Materials: General, 1974 August-October (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Report: “A Service Program to Retain Mentally Retarded Individuals within Their Home Communities”, 1974 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Report: “Budget Estimates, 1976-1977” (1 of 3), 1974 May 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Report: “Budget Estimates, 1976-1977” (2 of 3), 1974 May 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Report: “Budget Estimates, 1976-1977” (3 of 3), 1974 May 3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (1 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (2 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (3 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (4 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (5 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (6 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (7 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (8 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (9 of 17), 1974 April (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (10 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (11 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (12 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (13 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (14 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (15 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (16 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Report: Budget Requests for the 1976-1977 Biennium (17 of 17), 1974 April (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Report: Community Campus Day Care, 1974 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Report: Community Center Personal Services Schedule, 1974 May 20 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Report: “Community MHMR Centers, 1976-1977, Budget and Construction Estimates”, 1974 June (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Report: “Community Programs Patient Information System: Patient Movement”, 1974 March 20 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Report: “Community Programs Patient Information System: Summary of Patient Services by Organization Unit”, 1974 March 11 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Report: “Consultation and Educational Services, Fiscal Year 1975”, 1974 November (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Report: “Consumer-Citizen Participation Structure”, 1974 March 14 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Report: “Crisis Intervention and Mental Health Emergency Services”, circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Report: Drug Abuse Program, 1974 December (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Report: Expenditure, 1974 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Report: History of Programs Division, 1974 April 25 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Report: “Improving Health Services for McLennan County” (1 of 6), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Report: “Improving Health Services for McLennan County” (2 of 6), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Report: “Improving Health Services for McLennan County” (3 of 6), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Report: “Improving Health Services for McLennan County” (4 of 6), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Report: “Improving Health Services for McLennan County” (5 of 6), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Report: “Improving Health Services for McLennan County” (6 of 6), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Report: Navarro County Consultation Center, 1974 September (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Report: Out-Patient Program, 1974 April 25 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Report: Partial Care Services, 1974 February 13 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Report: Recreation Program, 1974 April 25 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1974 September (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1974 September (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1974 October (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1974 October (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 3), 1974 November (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 3), 1974 November (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (3 of 3), 1974 November (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 3), 1974 December (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 3), 1974 December (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (3 of 3), 1974 December (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Report: Sheltered Work-Training and Employment, 1974 April 25 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Report: “Sources of Financial Support and Organizational Information of Boards of Trustees Operating Community MHMR Centers” (1 of 4), 1974 September (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Report: “Sources of Financial Support and Organizational Information of Boards of Trustees Operating Community MHMR Centers” (2 of 4), 1974 September (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Report: “Sources of Financial Support and Organizational Information of Boards of Trustees Operating Community MHMR Centers” (3 of 4), 1974 September (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Report: “Sources of Financial Support and Organizational Information of Boards of Trustees Operating Community MHMR Centers” (4 of 4), 1974 September (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Report: “Statements of Program Philosophy, Issues, and Policies for Board Action Preliminary to a Work Session on the Alcoholism Program”, 1974 March 25 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Report: “Statements of Program Philosophy, Issues, and Policies for Board Action Preliminary to a Work Session on the Alcoholism Program”, 1974 April 30 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Report: “Strengthening Board of Trustee Capacity to Undertake Policy Planning” (1 of 5), 1974 February (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Report: “Strengthening Board of Trustee Capacity to Undertake Policy Planning” (2 of 5), 1974 February (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Report: “Strengthening Board of Trustee Capacity to Undertake Policy Planning” (3 of 5), 1974 February (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Report: “Strengthening Board of Trustee Capacity to Undertake Policy Planning” (4 of 5), 1974 February (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Report: “Strengthening Board of Trustee Capacity to Undertake Policy Planning” (5 of 5), 1974 February (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Report: “Summary of Modality Budgets” (1 of 3), 1974 June 20 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Report: “Summary of Modality Budgets” (2 of 3), 1974 June 20 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Report: “Summary of Modality Budgets” (3 of 3), 1974 June 20 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Report: Texas Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 February 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 February 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 February 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 February 6 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 February 8 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets (1 of 2), 1974 April 30 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets (2 of 2), 1974 April 30 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 May 31 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1974 July 24 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Report: United Way, 1974 May 22 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1974 January (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1974 February (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1974 March (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1974 April (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1974 May (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Reports: Monthly (1 of 2), 1974 June (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Reports: Monthly (2 of 2), 1974 June (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Reports: Monthly, 1974 July (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Vita: Ron Moen, 1974 September (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1975, 4
    This subseries contains materials produced by the Heart of Texas Region Mental Health and Mental Retardation Center in 1975. These include minutes, correspondence, and reports.
    The materials within this subseries are organized alphabetically according to type.
    - Application: Executive Director: Dean Mayberry, 1975 May-June 19 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Application: Executive Director: Dean Mayberry, 1975 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Application: Executive Director: Eugene Williams, 1975 June (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Application: Executive Director: Eugene Williams, circa 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Application: Executive Director: J.C. Doggett, 1975 June 3-16 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Application: Executive Director: J.C. Doggett, 1975 June 18-19 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Application: Executive Director: Richard de Santo, 1975 June 5-18 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Application: Executive Director: Richard de Santo, 1975 June 19 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Application: Executive Director: Richard de Santo, circa 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Application: Executive Director: Ron Whittington, 1975 June 1-16 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Application: Executive Director: Ron Whittington, 1975 June 26-27 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Applications: Executive Director: Rejected (1 of 3), 1975 May-June (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Applications: Executive Director: Rejected (2 of 3), 1975 May-June (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Applications: Executive Director: Rejected (3 of 3), 1975 May-June (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (1 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (2 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (3 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (4 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (5 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)